{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Faux Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40363/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40363,"taskName":"Specialty Painting - Faux Finishes","taskDescription":"Apply Specialty Decorative Paint Finishes","xmTaskDescriptor":"Faux Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":125,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Paint Special interior finish exterior","textMessagingName":"Paint Faux Finish","rolloverLongDesc":"More art than home improvement, specialty finishes are created by artists trained in the meticulous techniques required to create custom finishes that include stenciling, false wood grains, false stone \u0026 other effects. Most regular painters are not equipped to do this kind of intensive, artistic, hands-on work. Note separate category for murals \u0026 trompe l'oeil work.","rolloverShortDesc":"Faux finishes, sponging, stenciling, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Apply Specialty Decorative Paint Finishes.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Faux Finishing \u0026 Painting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Faux Finish Painting","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Specialty Painting - Faux Finishes","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Faux Finish Painting Project","urlName":"Specialty-Painting-Faux-Finishes","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Faux Finish \u0026 Painting Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Faux Painters","searchKeywords":"Paint,Special,interior,finish,exterior,decorative,custom,Woodstock,Faux,porch,stain,,room,wall,Finishes,Specialty","emcCategoryOid":-12054,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":657,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40363/":{"taskOID":40363,"originalTaskOID":40363,"setID":657,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5406,"questionDisplayText":"To be Painted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What do you want painted? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6766,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6504,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Trim/Doors/Moldings","answerDisplayText":"Trim/Doors/Moldings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1493,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Column","answerDisplayText":"Column","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2689,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Furniture","answerDisplayText":"Furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4205,"questionDisplayText":"Preparedness","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you know what paint effect(s) you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7165,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, I have an example to copy","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I have an example to copy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7161,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, I can describe what I want","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I can describe what I want","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4239,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No, I need a consultation for suggestions/options","answerDisplayText":"No, I need a consultation for suggestions/options","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5406,"questionDisplayText":"To be Painted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What do you want painted? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6766,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6504,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Trim/Doors/Moldings","answerDisplayText":"Trim/Doors/Moldings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1493,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Column","answerDisplayText":"Column","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2689,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Furniture","answerDisplayText":"Furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6766,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6504,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Trim/Doors/Moldings","answerDisplayText":"Trim/Doors/Moldings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1493,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Column","answerDisplayText":"Column","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2689,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Furniture","answerDisplayText":"Furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4205,"questionDisplayText":"Preparedness","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you know what paint effect(s) you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7165,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, I have an example to copy","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I have an example to copy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7161,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, I can describe what I want","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I can describe what I want","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4239,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No, I need a consultation for suggestions/options","answerDisplayText":"No, I need a consultation for suggestions/options","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7165,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, I have an example to copy","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I have an example to copy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7161,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, I can describe what I want","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I can describe what I want","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4239,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No, I need a consultation for suggestions/options","answerDisplayText":"No, I need a consultation for suggestions/options","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}